{"data":[{"question":"I never ________ to school on Sundays.","a":"go","b":"goes","c":"went","d":"don't go","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express a habit (Never).\u00a0\n- Subject (I) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. and Mr.Pike ________ dinner at the moment.","a":"is having","b":"are having","c":"are eating","d":"b & c are correct","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mrs and Mr Pike is plural\u00a0\n- Have dinner = eat dinner","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ eggs, bread and butter.","a":"is wanting","b":"doesn't want","c":"do want","d":"didn't want","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Does\/do: used with another normal verb to form questions or negatives.\u00a0\n+ Does: singular subject\/Do: plural subject.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"What time ________ he ________ lunch?","a":"does \/ have","b":"do \/ have","c":"is \/ having","d":"does \/ has","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Does\/do: used with another normal verb to form questions or negatives.\u00a0\n+ Does: singular subject\/Do: plural subject.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"I need a book but she ________.","a":"needn't","b":"doesn't","c":"needs not","d":"don't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the negative form of simple present tense (she + singular noun)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the Pikes ________ in the garden now?","a":"Is \/ working","b":"Doesn't \/ working","c":"Are \/ working","d":"Do \/ work","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The + family name: plural noun\n- Present continuous: used when you say that something is happening at the time of speaking\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ four seasons in a year.","a":"are","b":"be","c":"is","d":"am","answer":"1","explain":"\n- There are + countable plural nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ any sugar in the jar.","a":"isn't","b":"aren't","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- There isn't + any + uncountable singular nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs.Mary ________ me English.","a":"teaching","b":"teaches","c":"teach","d":"doesn't teaches","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\n- Subject (Mrs Mary) is singular.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"We have much ________ in the rainy season.","a":"rainy","b":"rain","c":"raining","d":"rains","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Much + uncountable noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}